In this section of the course, we are not going to talk about coding. Instead,
在本课程的这一节中，我们不打算讨论编程。相反，
we're going to talk
我们将要讨论
about mindsets. You're learning how to code because maybe you want to build an
关于思维模式。你正在学习如何编程，因为也许你想构建一个
app for you and your
为你和你的
friends or even you might want to build an entire business and replace your 9
朋友的应用，甚至你可能想建立一个完整的企业，并取代你的朝九
to 5. Whatever this
晚五的工作。无论
is you're trying to achieve, my goal with these following lessons of this
你试图实现的是什么，我在接下来的课程中的目标是
chapter is to give you
本章的目标是给你
the entire mindset that I've acquired in the past six years in order for you to
我在过去六年里获得的完整思维模式，以便你能够
achieve your goals.
实现你的目标。
We're going to talk about things like how to turn your idea into a reality as
我们将讨论如何将你的想法变成现实，例如
fast as possible so
尽可能快，这样
you don't burn out. We're going to talk about marketing principles for you to
你就不会精疲力尽。我们将讨论营销原则，让你能够
build a profitable
建立一个盈利的
business and we're going to talk about how to become self-driven, how to easily
企业，我们将讨论如何变得自我驱动，如何轻松地
find
找到
motivation so you want to show up every day and do the work. Let's begin.
动力，这样你每天都想出现并完成工作。让我们开始。